I'm Chmittens, black-tie silhouette
line-2
Three o'clock meeting hasn't happened yet
line-3
I watch very violently, perfectly still
line-4
Somebody has to run this windowsill
line-5
Chmeeze brings one thought to the floor
line-6
I keep an eye on him and one on the door
line-7
You need the keys? I've got the board
line-8
You need the table? I'm already yours
line-9
You stand to leave, I take your knee
line-10
That's not chance. That's strategy
line-11
I'm Mr. Inconvenient
line-12
Black tie, no invitation
line-13
Right where you're trying to be
line-14
I'm Mr. Inconvenient
line-15
Boss of the whole operation
line-16
But keep a little room for me
line-17
Door cracks open, my operation goes live
line-18
Tuxedo flying past a hand on either side
line-19
Left at the corner, double back, disappear
line-20
I won't surrender my hallway frontier
line-21
My strong meow could command a fleet
line-22
Then I start whining when the pets aren't complete
line-23
I climb in your lap; I've dropped the disguise
line-24
I'm black tie outside, baby inside
line-26
Black tie, no invitation
line-27
Right where you're trying to be
line-28
I'm Mr. Inconvenient
line-29
Boss of the whole operation
line-30
But keep a little room for me
line-31
Behind my watch, beneath my stare
line-32
I only want to find you there
line-33
Your hand comes down, my purr begins
line-34
I let the quiet take me in
line-35
I keep so close because you're home
line-36
I never want to love alone
line-37
I'm Mr. Inconvenient
line-38
Black tie, no invitation
line-39
Right where you're trying to be
line-40
I'm Mr. Inconvenient
line-41
Boss of the whole operation
line-42
Keep a little room for me
line-43
Door's open. I've got to go.